Fran: Parents don't often know, I
suppose, or don't realise, and obviously,
you know, your family life, things are
going to happen, but I think family
arguments, it's a big thing that
we come back to with young people.
And especially, I think some of the
older young people I work with who
are in their twenties and, and they're
sort of starting to realise at that
point that certain reasons that they
may be are impulsive or they're very
argumentative is because they heard a
lot of arguments when they were kids.
And yeah, one young person I'm
working with is particularly
coming up for me here in terms of,
he didn't know who his dad was.
And when I started working with him, that
was very much the focus of his, what was
going on for him is, "I don't know who
my dad is", "I want to know who my dad
is",  "my mum won't tell me", and "I've
never had a male figure in my life".
And yet mum, when I spoke to
mum, it was very much, "well, his
dad, his dad's an awful person.
I don't want to tell him in his dad
is", but what was, what was being
missed there was that there was, you
know, mum was having a very different
agenda to the son and they were
missing that they both needed certain
things that would have helped them.
And I think, I think sometimes parents
can really try and protect kids, which
is obviously the best intentions, but
that's having a real impact on them.